Love looks around to see who is in need, crying or lamenting.
You can see.
If you have that love, God will give you His face and eyes to see them.
The world needs to see our unity and our love for one another.
CAN YOU WATCH WITHOUT BEING MOVED?
The world needs to see our unity and our love for one another, if we have love.
The world needs to see our unity and our love for one another, if we have God's love.
CAN YOU WATCH WITHOUT BEING MOVED?
Your life, your success, your happiness, your progress depend on your willingness to help other.
How much you help poor is how much you progress.
CAN YOU WATCH WITHOUT BEING MOVED?
How much you help needy is how much you succeed.
Let us see the help to the widow, the needy, the poor, the refugee as a priority over any other help.
CAN YOU WATCH WITHOUT BEING MOVED?
For you to have peace, you need to be concerned about people around you.
Your joy and happiness depends on your willingness to bless others.
Love has a language
that transcends all languages,
all barriers,
all distances.
No wonder we are here today
in oneness,
sharing the Good News of our Lord, Jesus Christ,
irrespective of differences in race and tribes.